Guide to the Robert Alexander Papers 1962-1987 MSS 114
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Prints
  - Subseries A: Dance prints
    - Carolyn Lord, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Carolyn Lord, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Bruce McLean, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Meredith Monk, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Meredith Monk, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Meredith Monk, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Multigravitational Experimental Group, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Rudy Perez, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Rudy Perez, undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Rudy Perez et al, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Le Plan K, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Le Plan K, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Dana Reitz, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Dana Reitz et al, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Erik Roberts, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Erik Roberts, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Dean Selmier, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Dean Selmier, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Squat Theater, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Sylvia Whitman, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Oversize - Subseries A
    Scope and Contents note
    Prints mounted for P.S. 1 exhibition; Alternative Gestures, Dec 1978 - Jan 1979 (oversize)
    - Trisha Brown, Water Motor, performance, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Trisha Brown, Water Motor, performance, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bill Dunas, 30 Sep 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Douglas Dunn, Lazy Madge, performance, 1976 (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Simone Forti, Fountain Huddle, performance, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Simone Forti, 30 Sep 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - David Gordon/Pick Up Co., Not Necessarily Recognizable Objectives, performance, 1978 (2) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - David Gordon and Valda Setterfield, Times Four, performance 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Deborah Hay, solo performance, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Risa Jaroslow, 21 Oct 1978 (2) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Kenneth King and Carter Frank, RadeoA.C.tiv(id)ty, performance, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Meredith Monk and Ping Chong, Paris, performance, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Meredith Monk, Education of the Girlchild, performance, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Steve Paxton and David Moss, Backwater: Twosome, performance, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Prints for the Soho Weekly News
    Series I: Subseries B is a series of prints, arranged chronologically, of work done for the Soho Weekly News. Copies of the tearsheets from the newspaper can be found in Series IV, box 38, folder 38.
    - Sylvia Whitman, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Anna Halprin, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Anna Halprin, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - The Rockettes, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Rockettes, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Rockettes, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Rockettes, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - James Neu's Echo Ranch, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Echo Ranch, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Echo Ranch, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Echo Ranch, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Geri Atwood and Carter Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Geri Atwood and Carter Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Big Apple Circus, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Big Apple Circus, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - No Theatre Company, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - No Theatre Company, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Blondell Cummings, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Blondell Cummings, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Blondell Cummings, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Big Apple Circus, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Big Apple Circus, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Big Apple Circus, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Stuart Sherman, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Stuart Sherman, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Stuart Sherman, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Lucinda Childs, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Lucinda Childs, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Lucinda Childs, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Laura Foreman, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Laura Foreman, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Bill Dunas, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - David Gordon, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - David Gordon, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - The Hummers, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - The Hummers, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - The Hummers, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Jill Kroesen, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Jill Kroesen, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Jill Kroesen, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Mary Overlie et al, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Mary Overlie, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Dog'd Shots, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Dog'd Shots, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Donald Joyce, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Donald Joyce, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Donald Joyce, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Risa Jaroslow, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Whirling Dervishes, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Michael and Paul Galasso, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - San Francisco Mime Troupe, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Bill Gordh and John Malpede, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Dancing Songs, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Ann Cumming, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Ann Cumming, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Ann Cumming, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Tom Waits, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Maple Sugar, undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Kenneth King, Carter Frank, Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Kenneth King, Carter Frank, Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Kenneth King and Carter Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Kenneth King, Carter Frank, Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Kenneth King and Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Kenneth King, Carter Frank, Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Meredith Monk et al, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Eleanor Antin, undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Paul Zaloom, undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Paul Zaloom, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Peter Ustinov, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Peter Ustinov, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Yvonne Rainer, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Yvonne Rainer, undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - On Mount Chimborazo, undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - On Mount Chimborazo, undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Ellen Webb, undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Ellen Webb, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Ellen Webb, undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Ellen Webb, undated (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Ann Waldman, undated (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Subseries C: Celebrity and other portraits
    Peter Moore photographs; chimpanzee photographs for the NYU Physician; Kodak commemorative photographs.
    - Alvin Ailey, Nov 1978 (1 print) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Gerri Atwood and Carter Frank (4 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Ann Beckerman (2 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Ann Beckerman (6 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Peter Boyle, Feb 1979 (3 prints) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Lucinda Childs, Sep 1978 (4 prints) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bill Dunas, Sep 1978 (1 print) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Laura Foreman, 22 Jan 1980 (4 prints) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Simone Forti, Sep 1978 (2 prints) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Sheldon Frank (2 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Michael and Paul Galasso, Nov 1978 (2 prints) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Peter Ustinov, Mar 1979 (2 prints) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Tom Waits, Nov 1978 (6 prints) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Lab chimpanzees for the NYU Physician article on chimpanzees of The Gambia (5 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Kodak commemorative prints, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Peter Moore photographs (2 prints), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Subseries D: Portfolios and other personal work
    Series I: Subseries D - Boxes 7 through 11 contain prints from Alexander's portfolios. These photographs were not clearly dated by the photographer. Since the subject matter is varied and the dates uncertain the prints have been boxed in no particular order. Wherever possible however, prints that were grouped together by the photographer have been kept together in the collection. Box 11 contains oversize prints.
    - 9 folders containing portfolio work (mounted and unmounted prints)., undated (Box 7)
    - 15 folders containing portfolio work, polaroids, photographs of friends, self-portraits, photographs of New York City., undated (Box 8)
    - Portfolio (7 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Architectural (9 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Still life (5 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Street scenes, NYC (10 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Color polaroids - still life (3 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - School children (2 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Children dancing (9 sleeves), undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chimpanzees (1 sleeve), undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 35 sleeves of portfolio work from 1981, 1982, and 1983 (though dates are uncertain). These include self-portraits, domestic scenes, subway scenes, street scenes, portraits, still lifes., 1981-1983 (Box 10)
  - Oversize - Subseries D
    - 7 folders of portfolio work, undated (Box 11)
- Series II: Slides
  - Subseries A: Dance and performance
    Series II: Subseries A - Boxes 12 through 18 are arranged alphabetically. Of special interest are several sheets of slides, in order, of Stuart Sherman's Eleventh Spectacle (Box 16).
    - African dancers, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Geri Atwood, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Benefit, Dec 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Trisha Brown, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Yoshiko Chuma, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Circus, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Merce Cunningham, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Edwin Denby and Yoshiko Chuma, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Douglas Dunn, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Stephanie Evanitsky (Multigravitational Experimental Group), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Laura Foreman, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Simone Forti, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - David Gordon, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Martha Graham, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Grand Union, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Diane Jacobowitz, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Risa Jaroslow, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Bill T. Jones, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bill T. Jones and Kenneth King, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Judson Church, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Pooh Kaye, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Kenneth King, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mime, Victoria Falls, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Steve Paxton, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Red Mole Theatre, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Dana Reitz, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Rukas [?], undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Shelley and Denman [?], undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Stuart Sherman, Eleventh Spectacle, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Min Tanaka, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Paul Taylor, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Paul Taylor, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Torville and Dean, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Whirling Dervishes, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Stephanie Woodard, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Unlabelled mixed performance, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Events
    Series II: Subseries B is arranged roughly chronologically, though dates are uncertain.
    - Willowtown street fair, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Halloween parade, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - John Lennon observance, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Macy's Christmas, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Christmas party in garment district, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Thelonius Monk's funeral, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Christmas pageant, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Fireworks, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Opera in Central Park, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - New London fireworks, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: Portraits
    - Robert Alexander, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Ann Beckerman, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Trisha Brown, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Lucinda Childs, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Carter Frank, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sheldon Frank, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Philippe Petite, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bucky and John Pizzarelli, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Erik Roberts, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Rob Seiga and Toby Klass, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Peter Ustinov, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Tom Waits, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Mixed portraits, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Projects: 1973 - 1987, and other personal work
    Series II: Suberies D - These slides are arranged thematically and chronologically where possible. They comprise several ongoing projects, most of which document some aspect of life in Manhattan. Of special interest are the slides of the Alex Katz mural in the Attorney General's office. Box 25 appears to be a selection made by Alexander and the slides have been kept in the order in which he arranged them.
    - Movement series, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Ron Edson sculptures, Wids Delacour, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Alex Katz mural, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Mannekins, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Cabs, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Health clubs, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "From My Window" 30 sleeves of slides shot from Alexander's apartment window on 29th street, undated (Box 22)
    - Still life studies, 1971 - 1987; 22 sleeves (Box 23)
    - Memorabilia; 19 sleeves, undated (Box 24)
    - Unlabelled: 1 sleeve, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Kids mixed: 3 sleeves, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Views from my window: 1 sleeve, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Couples: 1 sleeve, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - City: 6 sleeves, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Portraits: 3 sleeves, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Workers and industrial: 2 sleeves, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Commercial: 1 sleeve, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - City, city people: 14 sleeves, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Subseries E: City People, 1973 - 1983 (dates uncertain)
    Separated Materials note
    Series II: Subseries E consists of one box of slides, arranged more or less chronologically.
    - 27 sleeves of candid photographs of people (mostly street scenes in New York City)., undated (Box 26)
  - Subseries F: City scenes, 1980 - 1986 (dates uncertain).
    Series II: Subseries F consists of extensive documentation of New York City (mostly Manhattan) over roughly six years. Includes photographs of the city bridges, the building of the West Side Highway, the city stations, street fairs, landmark buildings, and city parks.
    - 29 sleeves: Sep 1980 - Apr 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - 25 sleeves: May 1981 - Apr 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 28)
    - 29 sleeves: May 1982 - Dec 1982 (Box 29)
    - 27 sleeves: May 1983 - July 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
    - 12 sleeves: mixed dates, undated (Box 30)
  - Subseries G: Nature
    Series II: Subseries G includes slides of Maine, Long Island, Block Island, Novia Scotia, Utah, Colorado, and upstate New York.
    - 29 sleeves, 1971-1978 (Box 31)
    - 17 sleeves, 1981-1983 (Box 32)
    - 34 sleeves, 1985-1987 (Box 33)
  - Subseries H: Commercial work
    Series II: Subseries H is one box of slides of work done for jewelry and footwear catalogues. It represents a fraction of Alexander's commercial work in this field.
    - 14 sleeves, undated (Box 34)
- Series III: Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - Hillside nature shots, 7 Mar 1966 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 23rd Street, 15 June 1966 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Delancey Street, 20 June 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Personal: Diane; honeymoon, June 1966 - June 1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Diane, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Catskills campsite, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 5th Avenue, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Joan Berlin et al modeling for John Mandel, Aug 1968 - May 1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Picnic at Silvermine, 27 Oct 1968 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Gnarled tree, Atlantic Ave, etc, 5 Nov 1968 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Summer '69 photo course, summer 1969 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Ethical Culture School, 7 June 1969 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Personal, 1971 and 1973: Barbara (nudes), fern, rock, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Moon men on 5th, Mar 1971 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - S.E.L.C. march on Wall Street, April 1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Michael, June 1971 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Paul Kempf, June 1971 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Marty Mevado, July 1971 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Barbara, July 1971 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Various: Macdougals, Bronx Zoo, Jan 1972 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Various (including self-portrait), June 1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Wood stacks, skyline, Vivian, Aug 1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Central Park, Fran Atherton, Oct 1972 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Yarn still life, 6 Oct 1972 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Andre bakes a Christmas cake, 5 Dec 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Buildings lower Manhattan, spring 1973 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Architecture book, Oct 1973 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Multigravitational Experimental Group, Dec 1973 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Rudy Perez rehearsal and performance, Dec 1973 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Barbara Gardner, Dec 1973 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Meredith Monk, Education of the Girlchild, Dec 1973 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Carolyn Lord performance, interview, portrait, Jan 1974 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Trisha Brown interview, Jan 1974 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Trisha Brown rehearsal, Jan 1974 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Twyla Tharp Greatneck master class, Feb 1974 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Grand Union, Annenberg, PA, Mar 1974 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Rudy Perez publicity shots, Apr 1974 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Douglas Dunn, Piece 101, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Willowbrook, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Powers Nursing Home - Joanne Weisner dancing, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Various - Schlomo Karlbach etc, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Mulit-gravitational performance, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Maggie Kast and Carter Frank, May 1974 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Meredith Monk, Paris/Chacon, June 1974 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Trisha Brown, Art Now, performance, June 1974 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Trisha Brown, Ivan Karp Gallery performance, June 1974 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Wids Delacour architecture, 1975/1972 (?) (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Doug Dunn and David Woodberry, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Doug Dunn and Sara Rudner, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Bengal alarm clock, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Black light, Jan 1975 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Lawn chairs, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Wids Delacour, 1975, and architecture models, 1969, 1969-1975 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Personal - still life, building, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Grand Union rehearsal, June 1975 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Deborah Hay - portrait at Madbrook, fall 1975 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Doug Dunn, Lazy Madge, performance, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Andy DeGroat, Dickie Landry, Philip Glass, winter 1976 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Yvonne Rainer interview, winter 1976 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Flaming rock, Jan 1976 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - David Gordon and Valda Setterfield, Feb 1976 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Barbara Dilley at St Marks, Feb 1976 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - P.S.P.J. record cover, Feb 1976 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - David Woodberry at St Marks, Mar 1976 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Simone Forti at Fordham, Apr 1976 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Grand Union at La Mama, Apr 1976 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Barbara Dilley interview, Apr 1976 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Doug Dunn, Lazy Madge, rehearsal, May 1976 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Simone Forti at St Marks, May 1976 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Personal - wedding, summer 1976 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Sheldon and Carter Frank, Sep 1976 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Ann Beckerman etc, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Ann Beckerman, Sep 1976 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Personal - "detritus," 1976 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Push the War Button, Nov 1976 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Sylvia Whitman performance, Mar 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sandy Gross (?), May 1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Weed: A Rare Batch record cover, May 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Deborah Hay, May 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Ellie Dylan and Bob Atman, Sep 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Kenneth King, RadeoA.C.tiv(id)ty, rehearsal, winter 1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Personal - various, Feb 1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Geri Atwood; Carter Frank, The Baroque Rolodex, performance, Mar 1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Kenneth King at Brooklyn Academy of Music, Mar 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Anna Halprin, Mar 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - The Rockettes, Apr 1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Le Plan K, 23 Skiddoo, Apr 1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Echo Ranch, Apr 1978 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - David Gordon/Pickup Co., Apr 1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Wayside School - photos by Theresa and Sandra, May 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Wayside School graduation, June 1978 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Jim Burton, June 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Carter Frank and Geri Atwood, June 1978 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Big Apple Circus, 12 June 1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Squat Theatre, 20 July 1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - No Theatre Company, The Elephant Man, 27 July 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Photos by Robert Segal of Alexander loft, 18 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Robert Kushner's New York Hat Line, Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Lucinda Childs rehearsal at Delacorte Theatre, 14 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Charles Sheeler photos, 15 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Blondell Cummings, Cycle, 17 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Simone Forti and Peter Van Riper, MOMA Summer Garden, 18 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Jill Kroesen, 19 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Big Apple Circus, 22 Aug 1978 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Stuart Sherman, Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic), Sep 1978 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Art on the Beach, Sep 1978 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Group improv at Cooper Hewitt (Kenneth King et al), 5 Sep 1978 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - David Gordon, 26 Sep 1978 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Bill Dunas, Lucinda Childs, Laura Dean, Simone Forti (interviews), 30 Sep 1978 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Andrea Levine dancing jazz tap, 7 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Videocabaret - The Hummer Sisters, 8 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Friday 13th at MOMA, 13 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Dog'd Shots, 15 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Donald Joyce, 19 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Risa Jaroslow, 21 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Lucinda Childs at The Kitchen, rehearsal, 23 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Dana Reitz, 24 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - E. Monk Stenn - head shots, 28 Oct 1978 (Box 36, Folder 43)